comixology.com 2012-06-20

# Privacy Policy - Comics by comiXology

The privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) of Iconology, Inc. and its affiliates (collectively, “Company”) addresses Company’s collection and use of any User Information (as defined herein) that Company gathers when You interact with Company, including information gathered when You visit the Website, You register with Company, You use the Service or You interact with Company support.

All capitalized terms not otherwise defined herein shall have the meanings ascribed thereto in the Terms of Use.

Your privacy is important to us. We are committed to tailoring content to match the individual needs of our End Users and Retailers, but we also recognize the importance of protecting the User Information, including any Registration Data (as defined herein), we may collect about You. Company has developed this Privacy Policy in an attempt to balance our legitimate business interests in collecting and using information with Your reasonable expectations of privacy for your personal information provided to us when visiting our Website and/or subscribing to our Service.

Please review the entire policy to learn about what type of User Information Company gathers about You, how Company uses the User Information, what User Information is disclosed and to what third-parties and how Company safeguards Your User Information. Of course, feel free to contact us if you have any questions.

This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically so you are familiar with our current Privacy Policy. 

### Company’s Collection of User Information:

Company collects Website user information (“User Information”) in various ways, including (i) obtaining Registration Data (e.g. name, e-mail address, mailing address, credit card information, industry, occupation or other personally identifiable information) that You supply when subscribing to our Service through the Website and other personally identifiable information that You provide when You request information from Company, discuss a Service issue over the telephone with a Company employee, participate in on-line surveys, download the Software or a Software update, purchase other products or services from Company or otherwise use the Service, and (ii) obtaining preference tracking information from our use of "cookies" and other technology and other aggregate activity logging (“Movement User Information”). 

When You are an End User that registers with the Service or a Retailer that subscribes to the Service, Company allows You to create a unique account (“Member Account”) with an End User ID and individual password based upon Your personally identifiable information or a unique Retailer account (“Retailer Account”) with a Retailer ID and individual password based upon Your identification information, as applicable (hereinafter, a “Member Account” and a “Retailer Account” shall each be referred to as an “Account”). Company’s system will save Your User Information and use it to help identify You the next time that You log into the Service. The End User ID or Retailer ID is intended to save You time and provide You with easier access to the Service and other products and services. 

If You are an End User, Company also enables You to send e-mails via your End User ID to other Members and potential Members to share with them information about the Website and the Service and the pull lists. To fulfill your request, Company may require personally identifiable information about the person to whom you are sending the e-mail such as their name and e-mail address; however, the personally identifiable information that you provide about that person is used only for the purpose for which it is collected and Company will not use that information to market directly to that person other than what will already be presented via the text of the e-mail that is initiated by You. Company will, however, use software and other tools to track the frequency of activity of the messaging and quantify for its marketing and other business purposes the responses to these messages by potential Members (i.e. whether the potential Member has decided to register with the Service). 

If You are an End User and You use any bulletin board or chat room offered through the Service, make a pull list available to other Members through the Service or post a Member profile at the Service available for viewing by other Members, please note that any of the information that you share will obviously be visible to other Members and the information that You make available through a bulletin board or chat room or Your Member profile can be read, used and collected by other Members to send You unsolicited messages outside of the Service. Company is not responsible for how the personally identifiable information that You decide to share will be used by other Members.

As is regular practice on many company websites, the Website uses “cookies” and other technologies to help us understand which parts of our Website are more popular and how much time our visitors spend there. A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to Your browser from a web server and is stored on Your computer's hard drive. Cookies allow You to enter your password less frequently during an online session. We may use a separate cookie to track the Website's aggregated page views, which tells us which features are most interesting to our End Users. Our cookies do not store personally identifying information about You. Since cookies are now used as industry standard, most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but You can usually change Your browser to decline cookies. Our Website logs IP addresses and browser types (primarily for systems administration purposes), but we do not match IP addresses to any personally identifiable information. This means that Your Website session will be tracked, but You can remain anonymous in the public areas of our Website. You can browse those areas of our Website without entering any personally identifiable information and, therefore, remain anonymous during Your visit. If You prefer not to enable cookies, You may choose to disable them; however, please note that certain features on the Website will not be available to You once cookies are disabled. 

We also gather certain use information automatically and store it in our log files. This information includes Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, click stream data, operating system and date/time stamp. We may use this information to administer the Website, track movements around the Website, analyze trends and gather demographic information. The information does not identify individual End Users and Company will not use any of the information to market directly to that End User. 

Further, in some of our e-mail messages, we use a “click-through URL” linked to content on the Company Website. When an End User clicks onto one of these URLs, the End User will pass through our Web server before arising at the destination web page. We track this click-through data to help us to determine subscriber interest in this subject matter and measure the effectiveness of these subscriber communications. You can avoid not to be tracked simply by not clicking text or graphic links in the e-mail. 

Finally, we may use pixel tags, which are tiny graphic images, in order to (i) advise us of what parts of our Website You have visited, (ii) measure the effectiveness of any searches that are performed on our Website and (iii) enable us to send e-mails in a format that You can read and tell us whether e-mails have been opened in order to ensure us that we are sending messages that are of interest to our End Users. 

The Website contains links to other web sites. We encourage you to visit those web sites to learn more about their online privacy as they may differ from this Privacy Policy. Company does not control the privacy policies of other sites to which we may provide hyperlinks. 

To the extent that any Registration Data or other personally identifiable information is collected, we use this contact information for business purposes, such as responding to requests for information about Company and products and services, providing access to certain products and services, and for registration to Company. 

By submitting your information to us and by using the Website, You are consenting to our use of Your data as described herein and are consenting to the Terms of Use. If you do not consent, You should not register with Company and you should not use the Website. 

### Use of User Information Collected:

The User Information that we collect may be added to our databases and used for future communications regarding Website updates, new products and services, and status of membership subscriptions placed online. The User Information that we collect from cookies and browser identification provides demographic data about our End Users in the aggregate that we use to improve our Service and tailor our offerings. Personally identifiable information included in User Information, including any Registration Data, may also be used for marketing and promotional purposes for a statistical analysis of the behavior of End Users, for product development, for content improvement, or to customize the content and layout of our Website. 

In addition, we will, on occasion, send emails to End Users about our services or third-party products when you have expressed an interest in them. If You do not want to receive email or other mail from us, either choose to “Opt Out” and remove yourself from continued receipt of e-mail messages or send an email to us at [optout@comixology.com](mailto:optout@comixology.com?subject=Opt%20Out).

Our policy is not to share User Information with third parties other than as specified under the heading [“When do we Share User Information with Third-Parties?”](http://www.comixology.com/#share) unless required by law, or unless you explicitly request us to share your User Information with a third-party. We recognize that your User Information is valuable and we take all reasonable measures to protect Your User Information while it is in our care and will use it only as we set forth in this policy.

### When do we Share User Information with Third-Parties? 

We may share your User Information with third-parties under the following circumstances:

  * ### Affiliated Business We Do Not Control, including Retailers that have executed a Retailer Subscription Agreement

We work closely with certain business partners, including Retailers that have executed a Retailer Subscription Agreement. Part of the value of the Service is that we can provide the information in an End User’s pull lists and other general ordering information and information about End User use of the Website to Retailers.

In addition, if You are an End User and You fill out forms or otherwise provide us with Registration Data or other personally identifiable information and You, "Opt-in" to receive information about your area Retailers, we may provide your Registration Data or other personally identifiable information to the area Retailers that have executed a Retailer Subscription Agreement with the Company so that they can provide a service to You, including making the comic books on Your pull lists available to You. In this respect, these area Retailers may contact you directly about comic books that they have available or other products and services that may be of interest. These area Retailers may also further solicit You in the future.

Should you fill out forms or otherwise provide us with Registration Data or other personally identifiable information and choose to access other products or services offered directly through our Website or through the website of one of our business partners, we may also share Your information with certain of our business partners offering these products or services who may in turn solicit you in the future. For example, if You create or use a comiXology login on the Website or a comiXology-compatible login on the website of one of our business partners and You use either such login to access a product or service provided by us or by our business partner, we may share User Information, such as your e-mail address and your opt-in/opt-out status, with our business partner. Such sharing of information is intended for Your convenience so that You experience seamless continuity when transferring between the products and services we provide and the products and services our business partners provide.

  * ### Business Transfers

As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy assets. In such transactions, subscriber information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the unlikely event that Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, End User and Retailer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.

  * ### Protection of Company and Others

We release User Information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Use, the EULA, the Retailer Subscription Agreement and other agreements; or to protect the rights, property, or safety of Company, our End Users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection.

  * ### Aggregate Site Use Information

We may release aggregate Site User Information (without revealing any personally identifiable information about You) to advertisers and other third-parties in order to describe use of the Website and otherwise promote the user experience on the Website and share the results of pull lists.

By submitting Your information to us, You are consenting to the uses we describe above. If You do not consent to these uses, we suggest you opt out where available, activate blocking technology if available in your browser, choose not to submit your data to us when we request it from You or otherwise choose not to use the Website.

### What websites does this Privacy Policy apply to?

This Privacy Policy applies to the Company’s Website only. There are links on this Website to other websites and this Privacy Policy does not apply to any other website that has a link on our Website. If you click on a link and leave our Website, You should check the privacy policy of that website.

### How Secure is the User Information?

The importance of security for all User Information associated with our visitors and subscribers is of utmost concern to us.  We use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personally identifiable information is required and otherwise exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of your information from your PC to our servers and ensuring the security of your information on our systems. To make purchases from the Service, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Safari, Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later or Internet Explorer which protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet.  Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we take steps to protect your information, Company can't ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or from our online products or services, and You do so entirely at your own risk.

### What Choices Do I Have? 

You can choose not to provide your Registration Data to us or You may choose to not fill out any forms on the Website. 

Should you receive an unwanted email or direct mail piece from Company, You have the option to “Opt Out” of future emails or send an email to Company as described under “[Use of User Information Collected](http://www.comixology.com/#user)” to be removed from future direct mailings.

### How Can I Access and Update My Registration Data?

Any party who has provided contact information may go to the Member Profile link located at [www.comixology.com](http://www.comixology.com/) to update his/her Registration Data. 

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If You choose to visit any part of the Website, Your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this notice (“Privacy Notice”) and our general Terms of Use, including disclaimers of warranties and application of the law of the State of New York. 

If You have any concern about privacy at Company, please send us a thorough description and we will try to resolve it pursuant to the dispute resolution provision of the general Terms of Use.  You can send an email to [privacy@comixology.com](mailto:privacy@comixology.com?subject=Privacy). 

Please remember to include your postal address, email address and phone number with Your correspondence.

This Privacy Notice and the general Terms of Use may change without notice, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Notice in effect at the time of use. If You have concerns, please check this Privacy Policy and the general Terms of Use before submitting information to the Website.
